Guide to the Video Free Earth Production Company records, 1971-1991 MS2041
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Leonard Braverman papers, 1971-1990; MS2041 Series 1; 11 Linear feet
  - Videotapes: Video Salon I - 1 cassette (3/4 inch U-matic), 1984-1987 (Box 1B, Videocassette 56)
    [From original finding aid]: master program; n.d; program features video shorts made by various artists from 1984 to 1987. Contains the following works: Litany of Addresses (NOTE: also in Series I, Compilation Tape no. 5 and in Series II, Videotape 13) By Isabel-Lee Malone; directed by Jamie Walters; 13 min.1987. This subjective narrative evolves out of Malone's life and is performed by the actress, using address and personal events as turning points in one's life;Preparation H (description in Series I, Tape 38);Out of Control (description in Series I, Tape 37);Luis' Nightmare By Leonor Chaves; video by Marie Womack; 9 min.1986. This is a story about those things that seem like nothing to others, but can really bug you. It can be a nightmare. Chaves is an actress who performs at the Gala Theatre as well as for radio, tv, and film;Take Someone With You By Chasen Gaver and Gideon Ferebee 1986; 5 min. Gaver and Ferebee collaborated on the performance, Stay or Go. This performance poem is an excerpt from that work. In this duet, the poets mention the "lines of communication that bound us together" and "to get mad and get even" against slips in humanistic progress;The Boat (description in Series I, Tape 10);Vicki Picks a Tie (description in Series I, Tape 51);Carribeana Festival 1985-1986 By Osiris Productions and VFE Productions; video by Rebecca Crumlish and Leonard Braverman; 8 min. Segments from the festiva, coordinated by Fondo del Sol Visual Arts & Media Center, features music by Image Band, Maria Rodriguez, Tulio Arias, and Luis Salome
  - Videotapes: What It Means To You: A Videotape on the Emergency Planning and Community Right-to-Know Act - 1 cassette (VHS), 1990 (Box 2B, Videocassette 57)
    [From original finding aid]: c.15 min.; U.S.EPA Pesticides and Toxic Substances; TS-799
  - Printed Materials:Production Files: Arlington Art Center, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Printed Materials:Production Files: Baja Fantasy, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Printed Materials:Production Files: Beat-General, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
    [From original finding aid]: folder potentially contains photographs, slides, or negatives
  - Printed Materials:Production Files: Beat-General, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Printed Materials:Production Files: Beat-General, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Printed Materials:Production Files: Beat-General, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Printed Materials:Production Files: Beat-General, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Printed Materials:Production Files: Beat-General, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Printed Materials:Production Files: Beat-General, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Printed Materials:Production Files: Beat-General, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Printed Materials:Production Files: Beat-General, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Printed Materials:Production Files: Beat-Brochure, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Printed Materials:Production Files: Beat-Distribution, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Printed Materials:Production Files: Beat-Distribution, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Printed Materials:Production Files: Beat-Distribution of Tapes, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Printed Materials:Production Files: Beat-Education Materials, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Printed Materials:Production Files: Beat-Photographs, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Printed Materials:Production Files: Beat - Press photographs, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Printed Materials:Production Files: Bing Take a Swing, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
    [From original finding aid]: (audio cassette in folder)
  - Printed Materials:Production Files: Collab, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Printed Materials:Production Files: Constant Interruption, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Crack Politicians, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Cuckoo Clock, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Cuckoo Clock Photographs, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Printed Materials:Production Files: Desk In Hell, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Printed Materials:Production Files: A Family All Together, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: A Family Five Years Later, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: A Family Five Years Later, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: A Family Five Years Later, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: A Family Five Years Later, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: A Family Five Years Later, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: A Family Five Years Later, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: First Lady Joan-The Remake, 1982 October (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Free Association - A Retrospective, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Gina's Dream (Washington Project for the Arts (WPA) project, 1985 September (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Have a Banana, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Human Rights Campaign, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Jack Guidone/Wanabeast, Rocket and Dogs I, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Jayva and Linda Show, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Litany of Addresses, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Louise Nevelson, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Memorial Service, undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Misc. Tapes (Business Production), undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Nothing At All, undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Preparation H - Commercial, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Rapunzel, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Real Estate Demo Tape, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Real Estate Questionnaires, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Real Estate Reference/Research, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Real Estate Town and Co., undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Rockets and Dogs II Video D, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: St. Lucy and the Pagans, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: St. Lucy and the Pagans, undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Selection of Shorts, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Stay or Go, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Talent Demo, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Third Side, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Thru the CRT, undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Printed Materials:Production Files: Thru the CRT Photographs, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: They Said She Had Balls, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Under Suspicion, undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Vicki Morgan, undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Video Album, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Video Interviews, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Washington Wives, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: What Can a Poem Do?, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: The Woman's Patrol, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Young Audiences (Gaver Perf at Soussa JHS), 1987 March (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: AD Designs, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Budget Forms, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Copyright Forms and Regulations, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Copyright Forms and Regulations, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: DC TV editing class, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Distribution Contacts, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Printed Materials:Production Files: Duplication Forms, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Printed Materials:Production Files: Ford, Greg, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Printed Materials:Production Files: Misc.-Business Transactions (Record of Individual Accts/Clients), undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Printed Materials:Production Files: Misc.-Business Transactions (Record of Individual Accts/Clients), undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Parallel Lines, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Porr, John, undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Porr, John, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Porr, John, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Porr, John, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Projects: Proposed Ideas, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Record of Misc. Job Descriptions, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Release Forms Sample Contracts, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Tape Labels, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: VFE Brochure, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: VFE Letterhead/Business Cards (original), undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Printed Materials: Production Files: Video Order Forms, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Printed Materials: Public Relations: Advertisement (VFE-PR), undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Printed Materials: Public Relations: Distribution-Administration (VFE-PR), undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Printed Materials: Public Relations: Distribution-Certification, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Printed Materials: Public Relations: Distribution-Distributors Art Com (VFE-PR), undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Printed Materials: Public Relations: Distribution-Distributors-Misc. Correspond. (VFE-PR), undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Printed Materials: Public Relations: Distribution-Distributors-Parallel Lines, undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Printed Materials: Public Relations: Distribution-Distributors/Programmers, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Printed Materials: Public Relations: Distribution-Festivals Entered (VFE-PR), undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Printed Materials: Public Relations: Labels for Sold Tapes, undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Printed Materials: Public Relations: Mailing List (VFE-PR), undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Printed Materials:Public Relations: Post Card Template (VFE-PR), undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Printed Materials: Public Relations: Press Kit-Beat, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Printed Materials: Public Relations: Press Releases (VFE-PR), undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Printed Materials:Public Relations: Presentations/Shows (VFE-PR), undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Printed Materials: Public Relations: Reviews-VFE, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Printed Materials: Public Relations: VFE Business Mailing List, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Printed Materials: Public Relations: VFE Rate Sheet (VFE-PR), undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Printed Materials: Public Relations: Videotape Orders, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Printed Materials: Public Relations: Videotape Program Brochure (VFE-PR), undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Printed Materials: Photographs: A Family All Together Photographs, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Printed Materials: Photographs: A Family All Together Photographs, undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Printed Materials:Photographs: A Family Five Years Later Photographs, undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Printed Materials: Photographs: A Family Five Years Later Photographs, undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Printed Materials: Photographs: Fresh, Baja, Gloria, Vicki, Under, Louise Photographs, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Printed Materials: Photographs: Gaver, Chasen - Photographs, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Printed Materials: Photographs: Gaver, Chasen - Photographs, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Printed Materials: Photographs: Selection of Shorts Photographs, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
    [From original finding aid]: (Joan, Jackie, Capitol Hill, 5yrs and Family Video Stills) and Guestbook
  - Printed Materials:Photographs: Selection of Shorts Photographs, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
    [From original finding aid]: (Joan, Jackie, Capitol Hill, 5yrs, and Family Video Stills) and Guestbook
  - Printed Materials: Photographs: Video Salon I, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Printed Materials: Photographs: Scrap Book 1: Press Clips, 1980-1987 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Printed Materials: Photographs: Scrap Book 2: Press Clips (Program Descriptions), 1988 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Printed Materials: Photographs: Scrap Book 3: Video Free Earth: A Pictorial History, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Printed Materials: Oversized Materials: Gaver, Chasen - Performance Clippings, 1978-1985 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Printed Materials:Oversized Materials: Gaver, Chasen - Photographs - Black and White 11x14: 15, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Printed Materials: Oversized Materials: Gaver, Chasen - Photographs - Color 11x14: 5, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Printed Materials: Oversized Materials: Life Magazine, 1971 June 11 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Printed Materials: Oversized Materials: Poster, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Kenneth Rothschild papers, 1981-1991; MS2041 Series 2; 7 Linear feet
  This series consists of videotapes and printed materials including artist's resumés and publicity photos, scripts, correspondence, and grant applications. The material relates primarily to Video Free Earth business records. The material dates from 1981-91.
  - Videotape: Bike Pants - 1 cassette (VHS); original VFE Productions, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Videotape: Business Tape (VFE Productions ): Stock Tape #4 (Business Tape), undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
    [From original finding aid]: channel 1 - music and channel 2 - mix - 1 cassette (VHS); R.E. demo
  - Videotape: Business Tape (VFE Productions ): Stock Tape #4 (Business Tape), undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Videotape: Commercials/June East Special - 1 cassette (VHS), 1986 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    [From original finding aid]: includes shot list taped to side of box 1986 New Year's Eve Excerpts: Venician Real Estate; Preparation H Commercial (NOTE: also in Series I, Compilation Tape no. 5, Video Salon I and Videotape no. 38 and in Series II, Videotape no. 13; detailed description in Series I, Videotape no. 38); Pam Swarthmore - "Fucked up Babies"; June East Special (NOTE: also in Series II, Videotape no. 10); Tongue Wash Steps; Bell Ringers; Kisses; Ital. Church Frenzy; "The Slap" Piano Concerto; Heart Surgery (Face of Death); Faces of Reality
  - Videotape: Desk in Hell - 1 cassette (VHS), undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
    [From original finding aid]: VFE Productions (NOTE: also in Series I, Compilation Tape no. 3, Jamie Walters Retrospective and Videotape no. 23; detailed description in Series I, Videotape no. 23)
  - Videotape: Downtown Nobodies, 1988 July (Box 12, Folder 6)
    [From original finding aid]: Show for Charles Epps - 1 cassette (VHS); with special effects; includes shot list taped to side of box
  - Videotape: New Year's Eve - 1 cassette (VHS), 1988 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    [From original finding aid]: master dub; includes shot list taped to side of box: Lilt Commercial; Goddess Farewell 1988 Star Goddess + Bad Girls; News Gems - Joseph Lanz; Tiffany; Marlboro, Chatty Kathy; Lesbian Bed Death; Barbara Hutton - CB - Streisand - Million $ Baby; Face of Faith; 976-CHAT; Heat Wave; Shoot Me; Oh What a Relief It Is
  - Videotape: New Year's Eve- 1 cassette (VHS), 1988 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    [From original finding aid]: includes shot list taped to side of box: Show Music (no video); Goddess Farewell Video; "I Will Survive"; I Need a Man Christine; Backgammon for Blood; Trash Bag Fashions; Come On Get Happy (David V. as Judy G.).; My Guy (Lenny in black face); Apt. Tour of R + L; The Maid Quit; Grace Jones - Music Only; Finale - News Items; Roy Orbison; Joan Quigley; Pretty Woman - Music Only.; Lenny as Sukreet Gabel
  - Videotape: New Year's Eve- 1 cassette (VHS), 1990 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    [From original finding aid]: master dub; includes shot list taped to side of box: Goddess Farewell (Lenny as Christine).; Lotte Buff 1990 Goddess (Eartha Kitt: My Discarded Men); Tit Clamps - Version 1 with credits; Josephine Baker - Banana Dance - Music only; Les Femmes Perdues (NOTE: also in Series I, Compilation Tape no. 5).; Advocate Men Mag - Music - "See About Me"; Kitty Dukakis - Xmas Party; Opra - Background; Tit Clamps - Version 2 with interviews.; Jayva and Linda Promo; Bad Girls Backup for "Our Day Will Come"; Eartha Kitt - Cha-Cha Heels - Music only
  - Videotape: New Year's Show (VFE) - 1 cassette (VHS), 1990 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    [From original finding aid]: includes shot list taped to side of box: Lotte Buff Farewell; Pieter - Marlene Dietrich; Brenda Files - 1991 Goddess; They Said She Had Balls (NOTE: also in Series I, Compilation Tapes no. 2 and 7 and in Series II, Videotape no. 12); Doug's Lesson; Pima the Magnificent + The Cossack Women (in Russian); Sharon Dixon - Never Meant to Turn You On - Music only; A Boy This House (Country) (Rockaby Sweet Baby James); These Boots Are Made for Walking; Oy, It's So Humid; Doug's Lesson 2; June East (NOTE: Also in Series II, Videotape no. 4).; Titan Phillies (NOTE: [Titled Phillie Titans in Braverman Series I] - c. :16 sec.; n.d. (NOTE: also in Series I, Compilation Tapes no. 2 and 7 and in Series II, Videotape no. 12); Leona Helmsley; Marla and Ivana - Music only; Crack Politicians (NOTE: also on Series I, Compilation Tape no. 3 and Videotape no. 20; detailed description in Series I, Videotape no. 20); Twin Peaks - Music only; Finale - Get Happy
  - Videotape: Reducing the Risks of PCBs (U.S. Environmental Protection Agency) - 1 cassette (VHS), 1986 February (Box 12, Folder 11)
    [From original finding aid]: on cassette label; c. 12 min.; titles: 1. Reducing the Risks of PCBs; 2. TSCA: Balancing Risk & Benefits; 3. TSCA (8E); 4. TSCA Inventory Update
  - Videotape: Rothschild Compilation Tape - 1 cassette (VHS), 1989-1990 February (Box 13, Folder 12)
    [From original finding aid]: c. 21:33 min.; dub; contains the following: Bike Pants Phenomenon - c. 13 min. 1989 (NOTE: also in Series I, Compilation Tape no. 3 and Videotape 9); They Said She Had Balls - 1990; c. 8 min. (NOTE: also in Series I, Compilation Tapes no. 2 and 7 and in Series II, Videotape no. 10); Save The Arts - c. 17 sec.; n.d. (NOTE: also in Series I, Compilation Tape no. 2); Titan Phillies [Titled Phillie Titans in Braverman Series I] - c. :16 sec.; n.d. (NOTE: also in Series I, Compilation Tapes no. 2 and 7 and in Series II, Videotape no. 10)
  - Videotape: Short Works - 1 cassette (VHS), 1982 (Box 13, Dvd 1, Folder 13)
    [From original finding aid]: includes shot list tapes on side of box: VFE tape 1: Fresh Out of Ideas (NOTE: also in Series I, Compilation Tapes no. 5 and 9; detailed description in Series I, Compilation Tape no. 5); Gloria's Point of View (NOTE: also in Series I, Compilation Tapes no. 5 and 9; detailed description in Series I, Compilation tape no. 5); Baja Fantasy (NOTE: also in Series I, Compilation Tapes no. 3 and 9; detailed description in Series I, Videotape no. 13); Under Suspicion (NOTE: also in Series I, Compilation tape no. 7 and Videotape no. 50; detailed description in Series I, Videotape no. 50); Capitol Hill (NOTE: also in Series I, Compilation Tapes no. 3, 6, 8 and Jamie Walters Retrospective; detailed description in Series I, Compilation Tape no. 3); Louise Nevelson Takes a Bath (NOTE: also in Series I, Compilation Tapes no. 5 and 8; detailed description in Series I, Compilation Tape no. 5); Vicki Picks a Tie (NOTE: also in Series I, Compilation Tape no. 7, Mayor's Show, Video Salon I and Videotape no. 52; detailed description in Series I, Videotape no. 52); Cuckoo Clock (NOTE: also in Series I, Compilation Tape no. 3, Videotapes no. 21 and 22 and Video windows 1; detailed description in Series I, Videotape no. 22); A Family Five Years Later (10 minute excerpt) (NOTE: also in Series I, Compilation Tape no. 4, Videotapes no. 25, 26 and 37); Preparation H (NOTE: also in Series I, Compilation Tape no. 5, Video Salon I and Videotape no. 38 and in Series II, Videotape no. 4; detailed description in Series I, Videotape no. 38); Litany of Addresses (NOTE: also in Series 1, Compilation Tape no. 5, Video Salon I and Videotape no. 34; detailed description in Series I, Video Salon I)
  - Videotape: Videowindows 1: Childhood Time - 1 cassette (VHS), undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
    [From original finding aid]: c. 54:12 min.; credits: executive producer, Margot Kernan; Bob Boilen, Christine Graham, Margot Kernan, Jamie Walters, Nancy Garruba, Garri Garripoli; features five stories of childhood: Cuckoo Clock; Gina's Dream By Christine Graham. Uses oversized papier mache figures to represent things in life that preoccupy us, such as money. Young Gina breaks the bonds and starts on the path to individuality; Hiding By Margot Kernan. A series of sepia-tinted still photographs projected on the video monitor while Kernan reads a narrative poem about a young woman's loss of innocence at her grandmother's house when she catches her with the gardener; St. Lucy and the Pagans By Nancy Garruba. A wacky swack at Catholic guilt. As Lucy dresses to go to an official function with her husband, she tells the tale of why she quit Catholic school; Picture Parents By Garri Garripoli. Examines the influence of television on the young mind of Peter Hubbard and the parental abilities of Dan Dowdall and Terr Nussbaumer
  - Videotape: What It Means To You (Universal Media for U.S. Environmental Protection Agency) - 1 cassette (3/4 inch U-Matic), 1990 April (Box 13, Folder 15)
    [From original finding aid]: c. 6:45 min.directed and edited by John P. Paige; executive producer, Jamie Walters; producer, Eric Kulberg; 90-04-0141
  - Videotape: What It Means To You: a Videotape on the Emergency Planning and Community Right-To-Know Act (U.S. Environmental Protection Agency): - 1 cassette (VHS), 1990 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    [From original finding aid]: c. 15 min.; 2 copies; Pesticides and Toxic Substances (TS-799) (NOTE: also in Series I, Videotape no. 57 and in Series II, Videotape no. 17)
  - Videotape: What It Means To You: a Videotape on the Emergency Planning and Community Right-To-Know Act (U.S. Environmental Protection Agency): - 1 cassette (VHS), 1990 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    [From original finding aid]: c. 15 min.; 2 copies; Pesticides and Toxic Substances (TS-799) (NOTE: also in Series I, Videotape no. 57 and in Series II, Videotape no. 16)
  - Printed Materials: Miscellaneous Files: Braverman, Lenny/Files index, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Printed Materials:Miscellaneous Files: Files Index, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Printed Materials: Miscellaneous Files: Correspondence, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 3)